bytewiki.com 2012-07-19

# Privacy Policy

We are strongly comitted to protecting the privacy of our visitors. The following policy outlines the type of data that may gather about you and the way we may use and don’t use it.

## Information Collected:

Any personal information you provide to us when you visit a page or post a comment on the site will not be released, sold or rented to any entity or indivisuals outside Bytewiki.com. We, like most other websites, only collect user names and your email address when you subscribe to our news letter. Apart from that we utilize JavaScript-based tracking softwares, including Google Analytics and statcounter to gauge demographics and other relevant information of our site visitors.

Bytewiki.com will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on our site.

## Cookie:

We use third party advertisments like Google Adsense and infolinks to support our site. Google, as a third-party vendor makes use of cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Bytewiki.com users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

> A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in the user’s browser from a web server and is stored on a user’s computer, used to store and track information about the user. Bytewiki.com utilizes basic cookies to enable caching of our content in your browser to help accelerate page loading performance. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and we not use cookies to collect personal information. You can always disable cookie storage via your browser’s content settings.

We are not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Bytewiki.com and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Bytewiki.com have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

For further queries, you can reach us at:  
_contact@bytewiki.com_
